You
Hey, what's up?
You want to practice with me?
Don't look at me like that. Do do I want to do what with you practice?
For blocking practice. It's free practice time. You want to do something besides shagging balls, right?
Look if you don't want to it's fine. Sookie's coming too!
Glad you could join us!
Sweet! Put those down first. Oh
Oh
Hey
We'll be right back.
I haven't seen the video yet.
How did Shiratorizawa lose to you?
Was Ushuaka off his game or something?
He seemed to play just fine to me.
Yeah?
Then how do you explain the loss?
What kind of tricks did you play?
Or did someone actually stop him?
Honestly, yeah, someone did stop him.
If you can call what Hinata did a stop.
Who did?
What year is he in?
What's his name?
Where did he go to middle school?
Sorry about him.
He's just an incredibly serious pessimist, guys.
If someone is ever a threat to him, he gets freaked out and he loses his mind.
I'm not a pessimist at all.
I'm simply cautious.
Is that why you haven't actually given 100% here yet?
What makes you say that?
It's just a hunch.
I'd say you've been about average here so far.
He's convinced that there's been something terribly wrong with his shoulders lately.
But, well, of course, in his case, it's usually all in his head.
That said, there's nothing wrong with being cautious, is there?
Bath time.
Huh?
Already?
I'm getting in and out before anyone else can fill the tub with their charms.
Sorry to bug you guys.
Oh, man.
He's one of the top three in Japan, and you call him average?
I said that he's been average so far.
Everyone here is really good.
And that guy there has been great.
I wonder who he is.
But, you know, this first year training camp has been something else.
To be honest, I'm not really sure why Coach is having it.
Hmm.
I don't know.
I think Coach Washijo is just trying to change.
Otherwise, he would have never given a second thought to holding an elite camp.
And if he had held one, he certainly wouldn't have considered making you the head coach of it.
Think about it.
That said, something has been different about him ever since the game against Karasuno.
You think maybe their number 10 got into his head?
Well, the kid's definitely on his radar now.
Because, come on, man.
Did you see the look Coach Washijo had when number 10 got that last point?
That look I won't be forgetting anytime soon.
I mean, I expected to see him mortified.
But instead, I saw something else.
Thanks for waiting.
Here are your raw oysters.
There they are.
Mmm.
Hey, you better be careful with those.
You remember that time when our high school coach wound up with food poisoning?
And we all got to enjoy freak practice for the next day on.
Ah, such sweet memories.
Mmm.
Oh.
Left side!
Got it!
Hang on a second.
Hinata, you're not a libero?
Huh?
You think I could be a libero?
You think I'm good at receiving?
Oh, no.
I didn't really mean it like that.
Wait, then what did you mean?
I want to block two.
Two middle blockers?
If the ball comes to me, I'll slam it down on their faces.
Ah!
Ooh, me too.
Seriously?
Ahem.
Bring it on.
I'll block anything.
Same over here.
Ahem.
Damn.
Am I the shortest one here?
That was so cool!
Our side placement was wrong for that play.
The line shot was open.
Ah!
Well, I was sure he was going to do a cross shot, okay?
Yeah, me too.
Same here.
I thought it looked like a cross shot as well.
He even ran in a zigzag, like he was getting ready to do a cut.
He really is good.
I heard he hasn't been playing volleyball long either.
The date tech training shows.
He's not jumping around at random.
Hey, Tsukishima.
So, before, when you invited me to play, did you do it so I'd get a chance to spike?
No.
Okay.
At the Nationals, when we're playing against those high-level teams, the battles between blockers and spikers are going to be even more intense.
But tactics aside, it's clear that Hinata is a spiker who knows how to read a block.
I'd be an idiot not to practice against him.
Got it!
Nice kill!
If the ball is going to go over the net, you don't have to worry about making a perfect pass.
Yes, sir!
And that was a nice set, Kageyama.
But you can stand a little farther from the net.
What?
Yes, sir!
That was a nice kill.
Kageyama there.
He had no trouble whatsoever adjusting to a lefty-middle blocker.
His technique and game sets are both phenomenal.
How is that set?
Hmm.
I think I could probably hit it a little bit faster.
So a little zippier, maybe?
And, like, more compact?
I can do that.
He just says, I can do that, and then he actually does it?
That's kind of spooky.
So, um, keep passing.
Just like that, okay?
You got it.
I'm pretty sure communication is not Kageyama's strong suit.
But you can tell that he's actually trying.
Front! Front!
Nice!
Left!
That was high!
Oh, that was high.
That was in.
Fantastic.
Make sure you stretch properly, guys.
Hey.
So, like, do you recognize me or know who the hell I am?
Yeah, we met the first day I got here.
That's not what I meant, bro.
What I'm asking you is whether or not you've seen any of my games before.
Don't think so.
There's another guy trying to pick a fight with Kageyama.
Freak out a little bit, all right?
Be shocked!
You've been all staring at me like,
since the second I walked in the damn door!
Most people just assume that I can't hack it because of how small I am.
Then they see me play and totally freak out!
That is the normal course of events, okay?
This guy's gonna be real fun to put up with.
I am freaking out.
Hmm?
But also, learning from you, too.
Ha!
Well, well, well, well.
You have nerves of steel.
Setter.
Second year.
Latsumu Miya.
You know, Kageyama, my first read on you
is that you're as prickly as a cactus right down to the soles of your feet.
But on the court, well, you're just a goody-two-shoes.
Huh?
Here's your drink.
Thanks, man.
Where's my...
Hey, here's your towel, dude!
All right.
I totally forgot I left it there.
Thanks a lot.
Nothing gets past you, Hinata.
Oh, that's gone.
I'll go up and...
I'll go get it!
Okay.
Watching them play from up here is my new obsession.
Kunimi's receives look a lot like Ushiwaka's.
Every move he makes means something.
Shakuzawa!
Little help?
Or...
Maybe it's just that he doesn't like moving.
He totally just watched it fall.
Come on!
Show us your care, man!
You were supposed to go after that one.
We have the chance to play with a different group of guys here.
Get with it, man!
Go big or go home!
Uh, sorry.
I promise, guys, he does try hard when it counts.
Now, come on!
What's up?
You should have gone for that one!
Yeah, yeah.
All right.
Go get rehydrated and we'll do some two-on-two drills.
Oh, man.
I just can't handle that guy.
You mean Kunimi?
We're all working our butts off at this camp.
And he acts like he doesn't care about any of it.
But, you know...
He's super hard to beat when he starts going all out
after saving his energy during the first half of the game.
Still, if he can keep the ball in play, he should try.
I know!
He's taking it way too easy!
Uh...
Easy.
Huh.
Hmm?
Two-on-two, huh?
I'm not gonna lie.
Those are the toughest drills we do.
Yeah, when there's only two players out there,
you can basically never stop moving around, so...
But the guy who's got it the hardest of everyone
is the one sitting over there.
He has almost no experience.
I feel bad saying it,
but I don't really want to play with a two-meter guy.
Yeah, me neither.
He's tall, but he has the technique of a middle schooler.
Cleaning up after him is a real nightmare.
Gather round!
The rules are exactly the same.
Remember, when you're spiking,
no dinking the ball with the pads of your fingers.
First to ten points wins.
And I know I've said this before,
but always make sure you think about your next move.
You won't win if you play without intention.
Yes, sir!
Got it!
Ah, damn it!
That's how you're gonna play?
Kunimi's team is always really good on the two-on-two drills.
He's got good skills, for one thing.
And I can tell he's paying attention to his partner.
But there's something else, too.
I don't know why.
But I feel like he just doesn't get stressed.
Got it over here!
I feel like I'm getting left further and further behind.
Even I can tell my plays are getting sloppier.
Since there are only two of us,
it's hard to attack with anything resembling precision.
We're trained to watch the other team
and pounce on their mistakes.
And me?
God, I'm making a ton of mistakes.
But just knowing that
won't magically make me a better player.
Please, just let these two-on-twos be over.
Here's some water!
They really should have chosen you instead.
Hm?
What am I, an idiot?
He doesn't need me to point that out to him.
He's a starter for a powerhouse team.
Every person in here who's played against him
is watching his every move.
He's not some guy who's here for no reason, like me.
He came here on his own
because he wants to be chosen.
No, no.
I think you mean they should have chosen me too.
Don't you?
Everyone who got invited has something awesome about him.
Even you.
Like, you're huge.
Huh?
And for me, well,
without Kageyama, I kinda...
And I mean kinda
have a hard time reaching my full potential or whatever.
But still.
But my height is all I have.
That's all?
What do you mean, that's all?
Huh?
Did you know how cool it is your two meters tall?
If you told me I could instantly have
either an ultra-killer serve
or be two meters,
I'd get two meters in a heartbeat!
Huh?
I mean, I can always work on my serve,
but working hard won't get me any taller.
Come on, man.
Your height is
the number one,
the ultimate,
the most incredible,
awesome super talent there is!
Hmm.
You must be pretty confident to encourage a rival.
What are you talking about?
I'm just yelling at him.
Nope.
It looks like encouragement from over here.
Huh?
It does, huh?
Well, if that's how it ends up,
then I guess that's probably fine.
But how could it possibly ever help you
to make me feel better?
It helps!
Hmm?
Because I would like to beat you!
You know,
watching you guys from the sidelines,
I noticed something.
Would you be willing to maybe
try something out there for me?
Hmm?
Well, can't do anything
that would take a lot of technique.
No, it's easy!
I promise, it's super easy!
Cool.
Finish it!
Huh?
Third foot!
Ah!
The back…
It's wide open!
Huh?
Ah!
He can actually reach that?
Huh?
Ah!
All right, here it goes! Take it real easy!
Huh?
It's such a simple little thing, but it's easy to forget in the chaos of a match.
In volleyball, you can't drop the ball and you can't hold it either.
But when you or a teammate needs to get their head back in the game,
you can always try to make time for yourselves in the air.
Then, the pass you make when you actively choose to take it easy...
Got it!
...will make it easier on the teammate who receives the pass, too.
Well, I can't do anything that would take a lot of technique.
No, it's easy! I promise, it's super easy!
All you have to do is make the first pass as high as possible, like Kunimi does!
Just do that, and I think you can make the game a little easier when it's going too fast for you.
Then, once you've gotten back into your groove, it'll be like you can do anything!
Hand it over!
Anything at all!
Whoa!
I'm supposed to beat a giant in a head-to-head match?
You're so freakin' tall, you beast!
Hey!
Yakuzaa!
Nice kill, my main man!
Hmm.
You're so freakin' tall, you beast!
Ha!
Hey!
Yakuzaa!
Nice kill, my main man!
Now there's more of them.
Alright then.
You're free to go home once you've done your stretches.
Yes, sir!
Joe Roganori & No.
She'll be more of their distress.
Siraso had, she died.
He would work with me now.
Oh.
Now there's more神奇妙禒тиなど!
What do you wish could make her wish?
Was your BB with her?
That's why I wasn't willing to hit him with anime.
It's difficult.
He just didn't throw you.
We are
Next time
Hunger